Name: Shrijan Tiwari Address: 42 Thornleigh Road, Jesmond, Newcastle Upon Tyne, United Kingdom

Postal Code: NE2 3ET Mobile Number: +44 07436603316 Email: shrijansoftware39@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Graduated Master of Science in Computer Game Engineering from Newcastle University. I have over 4 years of work experience as a Front End Developer/Software Developer. My Technical Skills are JavaScript, Unreal Engine, Unity, TypeScript, Angular, Lua, C++, C#, React, Vue.js, LESS, Bootstrap, OpenGL, Java, SASS, HTML, CSS, Autodesk 3ds Max, Adobe Photoshop, Blender, jQuery and Node.js.

Link to my Portfolio – https://shrijan42.github.io/

Employment History

September 2022 - Present

Front-End Software Developer - Motivait (Newcastle upon Tyne, United Kingdom)

- Working as a Front-End Software Developer in projects such as Newcastle Helix and FFDT using JavaScript, Angular 14, TypeScript, Strapi CMS and SASS.
- Working as a Front-End Software Developer using Javascript, Angular JS, Angular 13, TypeScript, Mysql and Node.js in projects such as Zebra Island, Zebra Dashboard and BUS1016 .

October 2018-March 2020

Front End Developer/Software Developer - HiUp Solutions (Nepal/Head Office:Ireland)

- Develop and enhance frontend platform website/web application/API for Connected Portfolio-Premier-Education-Group and Apprenticeship.
- Design and develop new front end application for various platforms. Help out with front-end work on other application (HTML/CSS/Javascript/Vue/Angular in Node.js applications.)

March 2018-August 2018

Front End Developer/Software Developer-Deerwalk Inc (Nepal/Head Office:U.S.A.)

- Design and develop new front end application for Plan Analytics and other big data solutions based on U.S. health care sector.
- Feature, Support, Bug and Report Task in Deerwalk's Plan Analytics application and Executive Analytics applications using Javascript, Bootstrap, Java and Angular.

January 2017-November 2017

Web Developer/Front End Developer -Deerwalk Group Ltd. (Nepal)

Design and Develop web application for Deerwalk which includes Deerwalk CTEVT web application,
Deerwalk Library Management System and Hospital Management System web application using HTML
CSS , Javascript , Angular , Bootstrap , Typescript and SASS.

Education

Master of Science in Computer Game Engineering (2021-2022) (Date of Graduation: December 7 2022) – Newcastle University

Grade - Distinction

- CSC8501 : Advanced Programming for Games
- o CSC8502 : Advanced Graphics for Games
- o CSC8503: Advanced Game Technologies
- CSC8507 : Game Technology Innovations
- CSC8508: Engineering Gaming Solutions within a Team
- CSC8599: Project and Dissertation in Computer Game Engineering

Bachelor of Science (Hons) in Computing (2014-2017) (Date of Graduation: December 4 2017) - Islington College (London Metropolitan University)

Grade - Second Class Honours

- o FC6PO1NI Project
- CS6004NI Application Development
- o FC6W51NI Work Related Learning II
- CU6051NI Artificial Intelligence
- o CC1002NI Problem Solving For IT
- o CC1003NI Introduction to the Internet
- CC1006NI Introduction to Programming
- o CC1007NI Further Programming
- CC1008NI Personal Development for Computing
- o CC1HO1NI Study Skills For Computing
- o CC2005NI Project Planning and Management
- o CC2006NI Data Modelling and Database Systems
- CC2007NI Software Engineering I
- CC2008NI Object-Oriented Analysis and Design
- CC2009NI Communication Networks
- o CC2011NI Operating Systems
- o CC2018NI Professional Development For Computing
- CC2E01NI Employment Skills For Computing
- o CT1044NI Computer Hardware and Software Architecture
- MA1032NI Logic
- CC6001NI Advanced Database Systems and Development

Key Skills (Technical Skills)

HTML	C++	OpenGL	Node.js
CSS	C#	Blender	
JavaScript	Unity	Autodesk 3ds Max	
TypeScript	Unreal Engine	Adobe Photoshop	
Angular	Lua	LESS	
Bootstrap	Java	SASS	
Vue.js	React	jQuery	

Languages

Nepali (Native or Fluent), English (Fluent), Hindi (Fluent), German (Beginner)